skincaresearch.com 2018-01-22

# Privacy Policy « SkinCareSearch.com

## Privacy Policy 

Effective Date: September 3, 2013.

We are committed to advising you of the right to your privacy and strives to provide a safe and secure user experience.  This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, store and use personal information, provided by you on our website.  By accessing and using our website, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use and transfer of the personal information provided by you in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.  Please read this Policy carefully, as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law.  If you disagree with the way we collect and process personal information, please do not use this website.

**Information We Collect.**

Behavioral Information.  Is information pertaining to how you use our website, the areas of our website that you visit, what services you access, and information about your computer hardware and software, including your IP address, geographic location, browser preference, operating system type, domain names, times that you access the internet, and other websites you have visited.

Third Party Information.  Is information about you that we acquire from a third party, which may include personal, demographic, behavioral and indirect information.

Web Technology Information.  Is information we automatically collect from you when you visit our website.  This includes information collected from the use of cookies, Web beacons or JavaScript.

No Information Collected from Children.  We will never knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 13.  If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected Personal Information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database.  Because it does not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties.

**Use of Cookies, Web Beacons, and JavaScript.**

Cookies.  “Cookies” are a feature in your browser software.  If enabled, cookies store small amounts of data on your computer about actions you take on the pages of our website.  Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features you visit most often, and what content you viewed on past visits.  When you visit this website again, cookies allow us to customize our content according to your preferences.  We may use cookies to keep track of the number of return visits, accumulate and aggregate statistical information generally pertaining to our website, and deliver specific content to you based on your past viewing history.  You can disable cookies, although our website may not function properly for you.  Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set.  You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com.  In order to use all of the features and functionality of our website, you need to accept cookies.

Third Party Cookies.  When we allow third parties to display advertisements on our website, they can view, edit or set their own cookies.  We have no control over the practices of those third parties and are not responsible for their technology or tracking.  We encourage you to review the policies of such persons or entities on their websites.

Removing Cookies.  You have the ability to accept, decline or remove cookies, at any time, by modifying your browser settings.  Please see http://cookiecentral.com.

Web Beacons.  We use electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs, clear gifs or action tags) which allow us to collect information about your visit to our website, measure and improve the effectiveness of advertisements, and track delivery of advertising.  Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of page view, as well as a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides.

Disabling Web Beacons.  Because Web beacons are the same as any other content request, you cannot opt out or refuse them.  However, they can be rendered ineffective by either opting out of cookies or changing the cookie setup in your browser.

JavaScript.  We may also use JavaScript.  JavaScript is a computer language that enhances the functionality of websites, particularly in respect to pictures.  We use it to analyze and improve our website’s functions.

Disabling JavaScript.  You may deactivate JavaScript through your browser settings or activate it the same way.  If you disable JavaScript, you will not be able to use some of the functions of our website.

**How We Use Information Collected.**

Providing Services and Products.  We use the information we gather on our website to provide you with the services and or products you have requested.  This may include passing your information on to a third party to provide such services or products.  If you have any questions or wish to remove your information from the third party databases, you will need to contact that party directly.

Improving Our Website.  We use the information we gather to respond to any inquires you make, operate and improve the functionality of our website, and deliver the products and services advertised on our website.  Our services include the display of personalized products, content, and advertising, relating to your experience and interests.

**Disclosure of Information to Others.**

**We do not disclose your information to third parties, except as follows:**

Product and Service Delivery.  We share your information with third parties who help us in the delivery of the products and services you have requested.

Website Functionality.  We share your information with companies and individuals we employ to perform technical functions on our behalf.  Examples include third parties who host our website, analyze our data, provide marketing assistance, process credit card payments, and provide customer service.

Anonymous Information.  We share aggregated anonymous information about you, combined with other persons using our website with third parties, so that they can understand the kinds of visitors that come to our website, and how those visitors use our website.  This includes demographic information and behavioral information.

Legal Process.  We disclose your information if legally required to do so, or at our discretion, pursuant to a request from a governmental entity, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.

Acquisition or Merger.  We may disclose and transfer your information to a third party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets.

**Third Party Collection and Use of Information.**

Third parties collect and use information about you on or through our website in the following way:

Advertisers.  Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place ads on our website, may use their own cookies, Web beacons, and other technology, to collect information about you.  We do not control the use of such technology and have no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

Hyperlinks.  Our website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to websites owned by third parties.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites.  These links are provided for your convenience and reference only.  We do not operate or control any information, software, products or services, available on these third party websites. The inclusion of a link on our website does not imply any endorsement of the services, products or website, or its sponsoring organization.

**Security.**

We endeavor to safeguard and protect your information.  When you submit information on our website or to us through communications outside of our website, such information is protected both online and offline.  We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of personal information under our control.  The servers in which we store your information are kept in a secure physical environment.  The servers have industry standard firewalls.  Access to such servers is password protected and access by our employees is limited.  Please be advised that, although we take commercially reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure; therefore, we cannot and do not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure.  Any transmission of data at or through our website is at your own risk.  However, access to your information is strictly limited and not accessible to the public.

**Changes to Privacy Policy.**

We reserve the right to make material changes to the substance of this Privacy Policy.  We will post those changes through a prominent notice on the website, so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it.

**Your California Rights.**

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship, for personal, family, or household purposes (“California customer”), is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  However, under the law, a business is not required to provide such information if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its Privacy Policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

As stated in this Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by sending us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address.
